<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="urn:dita-ng:dita:rng:concept.rng" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="urn:dita-ng:dita:rng:concept.rng" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<concept id="glossary">
  <title>Glossary</title>
  <conbody>
    <p>Description of some of the terms.</p>
  </conbody>
  <concept id="genus">
    <title>genus</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A low-level taxonomic rank used in the classification of living and
        fossil organisms. Other well-known taxonomic ranks are domain, kingdom, phylum, class,
        order, family, and species, with <b>genus</b> fitting between family and species.When  where
        The scientific name of a genus may be called the generic name: it is alway capitalized.</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="pollination">
    <title>pollination</title>
    <conbody>
      <p><b>Pollination</b> is the process by which pollen is transferred in plants, thereby
        enabling fertilisation and sexual reproduction. Pollination is a necessary step in the
        reproduction of flowering plants, resulting in the production of offspring that are
        genetically diverse.</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="sepal">
    <title>sepal</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>sepal</b> (from Latin <i>separatus</i> "separate" + <i>petalum</i> "petal") is a part
        of the flower of flowering plants. <b>Sepals</b> in a "typical" flower are green and lie
        under the more conspicuous petals. As a collective unit the sepals are called the calyx, and
        the collection of petals is called the corolla. Together, these two structures are known as
        the perianth of the flower. The petals and sepals are usually differentiated into colorful
        petals and green sepals. The term tepal is usually applied when the petals and sepals are
        not differentiated and look similar or the petals are absent and the sepals are colorful.
        When the flower is in bud, the sepals enclose and protect the more delicate floral parts
        within. Morphologically they are modified leaves. </p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="rhizome">
    <title>rhizome</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>rhizome</b> is a characteristically horizontal stem of a plant that is usually found
        underground, often sending out roots and shoots from its nodes. Some plants have rhizomes
        that grow above ground or that lie at the soil surface, including some Iris species, and
        ferns, whose spreading stems are rhizomes. Rhizomes may also be referred to as creeping
        rootstalks, or rootstocks.</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="bulb">
    <title>bulb</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>bulb</b> is an underground vertical shoot that has modified leaves (or thickened leaf
        bases) that are used as food storage organs by a dormant plant.</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="cultivar">
    <title>cultivar</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>cultivar</b> is a cultivated plant that has been selected and given a unique name
        because of its decorative or useful characteristics; it is usually distinct from similar
        plants and when propagated it retains those characteristics. The word cultivar is generally
        regarded as a portmanteau of "<b>culti</b>vated" and "<b>var</b>iety", but could also be
        derived from "<b>culti</b>gen" "<b>var</b>iety".</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="perennial">
    <title>perennial</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>perennial</b> plant or perennial is a plant that lives for more than two years. When
        used by gardeners or horticulturists, this term applies specifically to perennial herbaceous
        plants. Scientifically, woody plants like shrubs and trees are also perennial in their
        habit.</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
  <concept id="panicle">
    <title>panicle</title>
    <conbody>
      <p>A <b>panicle</b> is a compound raceme, a loose, much-branched indeterminate inflorescence
        with pedicellate flowers (and fruit) attached along the secondary branches (in other words,
        a branched cluster of flowers in which the branches are racemes).</p>
    </conbody>
  </concept>
</concept>
